A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14 FA286
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Project Files, 3
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1938-1947 (Box 35, Folder 491)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1938-1947 (Box 35, Folder 492)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Building Requisitions - Insurance Policies, 1939-1942 (Box 35, Folder 493)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Disbursements, 1938-1945 (Box 35, Folder 494)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1938-1945 (Box 35, Folder 495)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1938-1939 (Box 35, Folder 496)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1938-1939 (Box 35, Folder 497)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1939-1943 (Box 36, Folder 498)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1939-1943 (Box 36, Folder 499)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Fellowships (K and V), 1938-1939 (Box 36, Folder 500)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Field Trip Memoranda, 1938-1947 (Box 36, Folder 501)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Field Trip Memoranda, 1938-1947 (Box 36, Folder 502)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Field Trip Memoranda, 1938-1947 (Box 36, Folder 503)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1926-1938 (Box 36, Folder 504)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1926-1938 (Box 36, Folder 505)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1926-1938 (Box 36, Folder 506)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1926-1938 (Box 36, Folder 507)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1926-1938 (Box 36, Folder 508)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1926-1938 (Box 36, Folder 509)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1926-1938 (Box 36, Folder 510)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1926-1938 (Box 36, Folder 511)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1938-1940 (Box 37, Folder 512)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1938-1940 (Box 37, Folder 513)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1938-1940 (Box 37, Folder 514)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1938-1940 (Box 37, Folder 515)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1938-1940 (Box 37, Folder 516)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1938-1940 (Box 37, Folder 517)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1938-1940 (Box 37, Folder 518)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1938-1940 (Box 37, Folder 519)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1938-1940 (Box 37, Folder 520)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1938-1940 (Box 37, Folder 521)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1938-1940 (Box 37, Folder 522)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1940-1942 (Box 38, Folder 523)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1940-1942 (Box 38, Folder 524)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1940-1942 (Box 38, Folder 525)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1940-1942 (Box 38, Folder 526)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1940-1942 (Box 38, Folder 527)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1940-1942 (Box 38, Folder 528)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1940-1942 (Box 38, Folder 529)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1940-1942 (Box 38, Folder 530)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1940-1942 (Box 38, Folder 531)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1940-1942 (Box 38, Folder 532)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1940-1942 (Box 38, Folder 533)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 39, Folder 534)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 39, Folder 535)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 39, Folder 536)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 39, Folder 537)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 39, Folder 538)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 39, Folder 539)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 39, Folder 540)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 39, Folder 541)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 39, Folder 542)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 39, Folder 543)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 39, Folder 544)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 39, Folder 545)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1946-1954 (Box 40, Folder 546)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1946-1954 (Box 40, Folder 547)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1946-1954 (Box 40, Folder 548)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1946-1954 (Box 40, Folder 549)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1946-1954 (Box 40, Folder 550)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence Index, 1926-1950 (Box 40, Folder 551)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Directors, 1938-1946 (Box 40, Folder 552)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Directors, 1938-1946 (Box 40, Folder 553)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Directors, 1938-1946 (Box 40, Folder 554)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1938-1943 (Box 40, Folder 555)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1938-1943 (Box 40, Folder 556)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1938-1943 (Box 40, Folder 557)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1944-1948 (Box 41, Folder 558)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1944-1948 (Box 41, Folder 559)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1944-1948 (Box 41, Folder 560)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1944-1948 (Box 41, Folder 561)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1944-1948 (Box 41, Folder 562)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1944-1948 (Box 41, Folder 563)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1944-1948 (Box 41, Folder 564)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1944-1948 (Box 41, Folder 565)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1944-1948 (Box 41, Folder 566)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1944-1948 (Box 41, Folder 567)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 568)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Newspaper Articles, January-February, 1938 (Box 42, Folder 569)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1946 (Box 42, Folder 570)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1946 (Box 42, Folder 571)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Statistics - Medical and Hospital, 1936-1948 (Box 42, Folder 572)
  - Farmington, Maine - Audit Reports, 1928-1929; January-December, 1940 (Box 42, Folder 573)
  - Farmington, Maine - Building Requisitions - Agreements and Orders, 1928-1929 (Box 42, Folder 574)
  - Farmington, Maine - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1928-1932 (Box 42, Folder 575)
  - Farmington, Maine - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1928-1932 (Box 42, Folder 576)
  - Farmington, Maine - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1928-1932 (Box 42, Folder 577)
  - Farmington, Maine - Disbursements, 1928-1947 (Box 42, Folder 578)
  - Farmington, Maine - Equipment - Correspondence, January-September, 1932 (Box 42, Folder 579)
  - Farmington, Maine - Equipment - Office Expenses, 1930-1932 (Box 42, Folder 580)
  - Farmington, Maine - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1929-1931 (Box 42, Folder 581)
  - Farmington, Maine - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1929-1931 (Box 42, Folder 582)
  - Farmington, Maine - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1929-1931 (Box 42, Folder 583)
  - Farmington, Maine - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 584)
  - Farmington, Maine - Equipment - Work Sheets, 1928-1929 (Box 43, Folder 585)
  - Farmington, Maine - Fellowships (A-F), 1929-1945 (Box 43, Folder 586)
  - Farmington, Maine - Fellowships (G-M), 1929-1945 (Box 43, Folder 587)
  - Farmington, Maine - Fellowships (P-W), 1929-1945 (Box 43, Folder 588)
  - Farmington, Maine - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1947 (Box 43, Folder 589)
  - Farmington, Maine - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1947 (Box 43, Folder 590)
  - Farmington, Maine - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1947 (Box 43, Folder 591)
  - Farmington, Maine - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1947 (Box 43, Folder 592)
  - Farmington, Maine - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1947 (Box 43, Folder 593)
  - Farmington, Maine - Financial Correspondence, 1930-1938 (Box 43, Folder 594)
  - Farmington, Maine - Financial Correspondence, 1930-1938 (Box 43, Folder 595)
  - Farmington, Maine - Financial Correspondence, 1930-1938 (Box 43, Folder 596)
  - Farmington, Maine - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Reports, 1926-1927 (Box 43, Folder 597)
  - Farmington, Maine - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Reports, 1926-1927 (Box 43, Folder 598)
  - Farmington, Maine - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Reports, 1928-1967 (Box 44, Folder 599)
  - Farmington, Maine - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Reports, 1928-1967 (Box 44, Folder 600)
  - Farmington, Maine - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Reports, 1928-1967 (Box 44, Folder 601)
  - Farmington, Maine - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Reports, 1928-1967 (Box 44, Folder 602)
  - Farmington, Maine - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Reports, 1928-1967 (Box 44, Folder 603)
  - Farmington, Maine - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Reports, 1928-1967 (Box 44, Folder 604)
  - Farmington, Maine - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Reports, 1928-1967 (Box 44, Folder 605)
  - Farmington, Maine - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Reports, 1928-1967 (Box 44, Folder 606)
  - Farmington, Maine - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Reports, 1928-1967 (Box 44, Folder 607)
  - Farmington, Maine - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Reports, 1928-1967 (Box 44, Folder 608)
  - Farmington, Maine - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Reports, 1928-1967 (Box 44, Folder 609)
  - Farmington, Maine - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Reports Index, 1926-1949 (Box 44, Folder 610)
  - Farmington, Maine - Minutes - Executive Committee and Governing Board, 1928-1949 (Box 45, Folder 611)
  - Farmington, Maine - Minutes - Executive Committee and Governing Board, 1928-1949 (Box 45, Folder 612)
  - Farmington, Maine - Minutes - Executive Committee and Governing Board, 1928-1949 (Box 45, Folder 613)
  - Farmington, Maine - Minutes - Executive Committee and Governing Board, 1928-1949 (Box 45, Folder 614)
  - Farmington, Maine - Monthly Reports, 1929-1949 (Box 45, Folder 615)
  - Farmington, Maine - Monthly Reports, 1929-1949 (Box 45, Folder 616)
  - Farmington, Maine - Monthly Reports, 1929-1949 (Box 45, Folder 617)
  - Farmington, Maine - Monthly Reports, 1929-1949 (Box 45, Folder 618)
  - Farmington, Maine - Monthly Reports, 1929-1949 (Box 45, Folder 619)
  - Farmington, Maine - Monthly Reports, 1929-1949 (Box 45, Folder 620)
  - Farmington, Maine - Monthly Reports, 1929-1949 (Box 45, Folder 621)
  - Farmington, Maine - Monthly Reports, 1929-1949 (Box 45, Folder 622)
  - Farmington, Maine - Monthly Reports, 1929-1949 (Box 45, Folder 623)
  - Farmington, Maine - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1941 (Box 46, Folder 624)
  - Farmington, Maine - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1941 (Box 46, Folder 625)
  - Farmington, Maine - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1941 (Box 46, Folder 626)
  - Farmington, Maine - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1941 (Box 46, Folder 627)
  - Farmington, Maine - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1941 (Box 46, Folder 628)
  - Farmington, Maine - Practical Nurse Training - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1946-1947 (Box 46, Folder 629)
  - Farmington, Maine - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1935-1940 (Box 46, Folder 630)
  - Farmington, Maine - Public Health Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1941 (Box 46, Folder 631)
  - Farmington, Maine - Public Health Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1941 (Box 46, Folder 632)
  - Farmington, Maine - Public Health Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1941 (Box 46, Folder 633)
  - Farmington, Maine - Public Health Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1941 (Box 46, Folder 634)
  - Farmington, Maine - Public Health Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1941 (Box 46, Folder 635)
  - Farmington, Maine - Public Health Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1941 (Box 46, Folder 636)
  - Farmington, Maine - Public Health Program - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1927-1939 (Box 46, Folder 637)
  - Farmington, Maine - Publicity - News Releases and Articles, June-October, 1927 (Box 46, Folder 638)
  - Farmington, Maine - Statistics - Medical and Hospital, 1930-1948 (Box 46, Folder 639)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Accounting Manual - Correspondence, January-May, 1932 (Box 47, Folder 640)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Audit Reports, 1926-1928, 1945 (Box 47, Folder 641)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Building Requisitions - Bonds and Contracts, 1926-1941 (Box 47, Folder 642)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Building Requisitions - Change and Purchase Orders, 1936-1942 (Box 47, Folder 643)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1926-1943 (Box 47, Folder 644)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1926-1943 (Box 47, Folder 645)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1926-1943 (Box 47, Folder 646)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Building Requisitions - Pre-Qualification Statements, May-June, 1941 (Box 47, Folder 647)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Disbursements, 1926-1942 (Box 47, Folder 648)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Disbursements, 1926-1942 (Box 47, Folder 649)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Disbursements, 1926-1942 (Box 47, Folder 650)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1927-1942 (Box 47, Folder 651)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1927-1942 (Box 47, Folder 652)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1927 and 1941 (Box 47, Folder 653)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Equipment - Work Sheets, 1926-1927 (Box 48, Folder 654)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Equipment - Work Sheets, 1926-1927 (Box 48, Folder 655)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Fellowships (A-F), 1927-1940 (Box 48, Folder 656)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Fellowships (H), 1927-1940 (Box 48, Folder 657)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Fellowships (I-M), 1927-1940 (Box 48, Folder 658)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Fellowships (N-W), 1927-1940 (Box 48, Folder 659)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Field Trip Memoranda, 1926-1947 (Box 48, Folder 660)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Field Trip Memoranda, 1926-1947 (Box 48, Folder 661)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Field Trip Memoranda, 1926-1947 (Box 48, Folder 662)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Field Trip Memoranda, 1926-1947 (Box 48, Folder 663)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1925-1928 (Box 48, Folder 664)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1925-1928 (Box 48, Folder 665)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1929-1946 (Box 49, Folder 666)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1929-1946 (Box 49, Folder 667)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1929-1946 (Box 49, Folder 668)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1929-1946 (Box 49, Folder 669)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1929-1946 (Box 49, Folder 670)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1929-1946 (Box 49, Folder 671)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1929-1946 (Box 49, Folder 672)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1929-1946 (Box 49, Folder 673)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1929-1946 (Box 49, Folder 674)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1929-1946 (Box 49, Folder 675)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1929-1946 (Box 49, Folder 676)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1929-1946 (Box 49, Folder 677)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1929-1946 (Box 49, Folder 678)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1947-1957 (Box 50, Folder 679)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1947-1957 (Box 50, Folder 680)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1947-1957 (Box 50, Folder 681)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1925-1950 (Box 50, Folder 682)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1925-1950 (Box 50, Folder 683)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Minutes - Board of Directors; Executive and Financial Committees, 1928-1940 (Box 50, Folder 684)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Minutes - Board of Directors; Executive and Financial Committees, 1928-1940 (Box 50, Folder 685)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Minutes - Board of Directors; Executive and Financial Committees, 1928-1940 (Box 50, Folder 686)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Minutes - Board of Directors; Executive and Financial Committees, 1928-1940 (Box 50, Folder 687)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Monthly Reports, 1928-1943 (Box 50, Folder 688)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Monthly Reports, 1928-1943 (Box 50, Folder 689)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Monthly Reports, 1928-1943 (Box 50, Folder 690)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Monthly Reports, 1928-1943 (Box 50, Folder 691)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Monthly Reports, 1928-1943 (Box 50, Folder 692)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Monthly Reports, 1944-1948 (Box 51, Folder 693)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Monthly Reports, 1944-1948 (Box 51, Folder 694)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Monthly Reports, 1944-1948 (Box 51, Folder 695)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Monthly Reports, 1944-1948 (Box 51, Folder 696)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Monthly Reports, 1944-1948 (Box 51, Folder 697)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1947 (Box 51, Folder 698)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1947 (Box 51, Folder 699)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1947 (Box 51, Folder 700)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1947 (Box 51, Folder 701)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1943 (Box 51, Folder 702)
    1940 Indexed.
  - Farmville, Virginia - Public Health Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1928-1933 (Box 51, Folder 703)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Public Health Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1928-1933 (Box 51, Folder 704)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Public Health Program - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1927-1948 (Box 51, Folder 705)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Public Health Program - Financial Correspondence and Vouchers, 1928-1934 (Box 51, Folder 706)
  - Farmville, Virginia - Statistics - Medical and Hospital, 1930-1948 (Box 51, Folder 707)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Accounting Manual - Correspondence, January-June, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 708)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Audit Reports, 1929; 1930; 1948 (Box 52, Folder 709)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Building Requisitions - Bonds and Contracts, 1928-1929 (Box 52, Folder 710)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1928-1934 (Box 52, Folder 711)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1928-1934 (Box 52, Folder 712)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1928-1934 (Box 52, Folder 713)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Building Requisitions - Work Bids, 1936; 1946 (Box 52, Folder 714)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Disbursements, 1929-1942 (Box 52, Folder 715)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Disbursements, 1929-1942 (Box 52, Folder 716)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Disbursements, 1929-1942 (Box 52, Folder 717)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1928-1931 (Box 52, Folder 718)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1928-1931 (Box 52, Folder 719)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Equipment - Work Sheets, 1928-1929 (Box 52, Folder 720)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Fellowships (A-E), 1929-1941 (Box 52, Folder 721)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Fellowships (H-P), 1929-1941 (Box 52, Folder 722)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Fellowships (R-Y), 1929-1941 (Box 52, Folder 723)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1946 (Box 53, Folder 724)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1946 (Box 53, Folder 725)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1946 (Box 53, Folder 726)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1946 (Box 53, Folder 727)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1946 (Box 53, Folder 728)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1946 (Box 53, Folder 729)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1946 (Box 53, Folder 730)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1925-1932 (Box 53, Folder 731)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1925-1932 (Box 53, Folder 732)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1925-1932 (Box 53, Folder 733)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1925-1932 (Box 53, Folder 734)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1925-1932 (Box 53, Folder 735)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1925-1932 (Box 53, Folder 736)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1978 (Box 54, Folder 737)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1978 (Box 54, Folder 738)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1978 (Box 54, Folder 739)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1978 (Box 54, Folder 740)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1978 (Box 54, Folder 741)